Dead Again in Tombstone is a western, action,
fantasy film directed by Roel Reiné.
The devil’s outlaw and reluctant servant, Guerrero returns from the dead again in
this action-packed western which promises to be one hell of a ride.
Guerrero is forced to protect a stolen relic from getting into the hands of Jackson Boomer and his gang of soldiers, but
Jackson will stop at nothing to raise his comrades from the dead and bring the wrath of hell upon earth.
Guerrero must use all his dark powers in order to defeat
Jackson and find redemption…or die again trying.
Guerrero, played by Danny Trejo.
Colonel Jackson Boomer, played by Jake Busey.
Alicia, played by Elysia Rotaru.
Bull Dog, played by Nathaniel Arcand.
Dr. Goldsworthy, played by Dean McDermott.
Madame Du Vere, played by Elizabeth Lavender.
Dead in Tombstone is a 2013 American direct-to-video horror
Western film produced by Universal 1440 Entertainment.
It was directed by Roel Reiné and written by Shane Kuhn and Brendan Cowles.
The film stars Danny Trejo as Guerrero, a gang leader who
gets double-crossed by his fellow gang members.
Striking a pact with the Devil after entering Hell, he resurfaces to the earthly
world to avenge his own death by killing the men who murdered him.
The film was released in home media on October 22, 2013, and was
followed by a sequel, Dead Again in Tombstone (2017).
The film is based on the concept of the deal with the Devil.
The tone is dark.